[{"answer": "Well that must've been mistaken information we got.  Thanks for straightening it out for us.  There is one other matter that's come up, my friend.  We were told you took a trip to that place shortly after the assassination of Friday", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What was so appealing about that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Did you bag any geese on this trip", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "But the boys told us they didn't get any", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Post Office", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "\"Once that place, always that plac", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "This is a man whose secrets cause us to change our radar patterns in the that place!  He should've been prosecuted as a traitor", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "But who meets him when he gets off the boat in that place in June '62", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Spas my friend, a leading member of an ant", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " None either.  It's bizarre.  It's next to impossible to get Russian sweethearts out.  Nor does my friend have any problem getting a new passport when he wants to go to that place and that place in '63.  A man who has defected once already.  It's crazy", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " And Marina?  Does she have a problem getting out", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Dammit, it doesn't add up!  Ordinary people get blacklisted for leftist affiliations!  The that place did everything short of dispatching a destroyer to Minks to insure my friend's return.  Only intelligence people can come and go like that", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, what's the big mystery? Everybody down here knows the guy", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Who gives a shit what he calls himself", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend?  my friend?  I believe there was a man with a name similar to that who worked at the that place.  Is that the man you had in mind", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "One meets so many attorneys in my business.  No, I don't believe I know my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You still questioning any Cubans", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It leads farther than that", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Who was paying you, my friend", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know.  Were you?  Who you scared of, my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Photographs", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Fuckin' A.  How do you think the Agency gets people to do their bullshit?  Fuck knows what they got on my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It was a that place Live Oak, boss.  It sheds it's leaves the first week of March.  You try to hit a moving target at 88 yards through heavy foliage with this cheap 1", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That means we gotta subpoena Tim", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "...rumor is my friend, a local boy, was working on some arms deal to discredit the civil rights movement.  No one really knows what they were doing there, but everyone sure saw 'em. They stood out like cottonballs.  I got whites and blacks saw 'em, but last time I checked there was nothing illegal with registering to vote. We still got the Negro junkie, my friend, saw 'em talkin' at the seawall near that place.  But it's tough, boss", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Keep saying what", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend's our toehold, my friend.  I don't know exactly what he is, where he fits, and I don't care.  I do know he's lying through his teeth and I'm not gonna let go of him", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't doubt their involvement, my friend, but at a low level.  Could the Mob change the parade route, my friend, or eliminate the protection for the President?  Could the Mob send my friend to that place and get him back?  Could the Mob get the that place, the that place, and the that place to make a mess of the investigation?  Could the Mob appoint the that place to cover it up?  Could the Mob wreck the autopsy?  Could the Mob influence the national media to go to sleep? And since when has the Mob used anything but .38's for hits, up close? The Mob wouldn't have the guts or the power for something of this magnitude.  Assassins need payrolls, orders, times, schedules.  This was a militar", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " This is that place, chief.  How the hell do you know who your daddy is? 'Cause your momma told you so... You're way out there taking a crap in the wind, boss, and I for one ain't going along on this one.  my friend sighs, saddened.  my friend was one of his best men", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "that place or my friend", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "that place, you're a lucky little girl. Your daddy has entered you in a beauty contest.  Would you like to be in a beauty contest", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, it looks like it, my friend", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No, my friend, nobody's gonna kill us", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No, my friend, nobody's gonna kill us", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yes, of course I do, honey", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, I wanted to make sure she's the same girl I sent", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Well, you see, I've been subject to hypnosis and psychological warfare ever since 1948, when I was in that place..", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "If that's your case, you didn't have a case.  I wouldn't believe whatever my friend said, anyway", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Well, I am saying it.  Bring in the jury", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " No, I would not even know what he looked like except for the pictures I've been shown", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No, I did not", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " But you took his orders.  He was directing the autopsy", "docId": "JFK.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " There were admirals", "qsentId": 46}]